# taken from open trivia: https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
question_data = [{"type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. "
                              "and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
                  "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered"
                              " together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, "
                              "musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters "
                              "shorter than the average man.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
